http://www.epiqtech.com/company/privacy-policy

Effective Date 19-DEC-2002
Epiq Technologies, Inc.
1. Overview.
This Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how this site collects, use and safeguards the personal information you provide to Epiq Technologies, Inc. and to assist you in making purchases.
2. What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use it?
When you visit this site you may provide Epiq Technologies, Inc. with two types of information: personal information you actively choose to disclose ("Active Information") through making a purchase or contacting Epiq Technologies, Inc., and use information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate anonymous basis as you and others browse this site ("Passive Information").
3. No Use of Our Site by Persons Under 13
No person under 13 should disclose information on this site. You may learn more about protecting children's privacy online by visiting www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy.
4. Active Information You Disclose For Purchase
If you make a purchase of software or services, Epiq Technologies, Inc. may collect your name, billing address, billing phone number, email and credit card information. Epiq Technologies, Inc. uses such information only for processing your order and to contact you via email if you indicated that you wished to receive an email notification of updates or new software or services.
If you choose to contact Epiq Technologies, Inc. via email, postal mail or telephone, Epiq Technologies, Inc. may retain such information also.
5. Passive Information Collected
Our site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how this site is used. Passive Information gathered may include the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at this site, the sites visited just before and just after this site. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie" information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the "Help" section of your browser to correctly do so.
We use Passive Information to gather information about this users and to enhance and design this site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use. Additionally, cookies help Epiq Technologies, Inc. know information about how many people visit this site, when they visit and how they use this site. We do not connect any of this information to your personal information or email address.
6. What is a Cookie?
Cookies are a feature of web browser (Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, etc.) software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on one site to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transaction on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.
7. Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law
We may be required by law or government agency to disclose both Active and Passive Information you have provided to Epiq Technologies, Inc. and will do so if required by law or subpoena, or for enforcement of or claims regarding our purchase agreement license.
8. How Do We Secure Active Information and Passive Information?
We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction, anathema to us, of Active Information and Passive Information. Other communications you may have with Epiq Technologies, Inc. via email or postal mail may not be secure unless Epiq Technologies, Inc. advises you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with Epiq Technologies, Inc. through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and Epiq Technologies, Inc. requests that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means.
9. How Can You Choose Not to Receive Information from Us or to Correct, Delete or Access Your Information?
If you desire not to receive information or if you wish to access, delete or correct you information, please send Epiq Technologies, Inc. an email to support@epiqtech.com.
10. Policy Revisions
We reserve the right to revise this policy at this discretion. Please check back on this site as this policy may be revised from time to time without notice to you.
/request-demo
REQUEST DEMO
Products
Procurement
Procure-to-PayProcure-to-OrderCompliant InvoicingGuided Requisitioning Back
EducationElectric UtilitiesFinancial ServicesFood & BeverageHealthcareManufacturingOil & GasPublic SectorRetail & eCommerce Back
Profit MaximizationSpend VisibilitySupplier RelationshipsRisk Management Back
Supplier ManagementSpend AnalysisSourcingContract ManagementProcurementCompliant Invoicing Back
Resources
Resource LibraryLive DemosSourcing & Procurement Guides Back
Services
ConsultingSupportCustomer SuccessTrainingChange ManagementAdoption & Growth Back
ComprehensiveSustainableOpenUser-FocusedFlexibleAccelerated Back
Partners
OverviewAlliance PartnersTechnology PartnersReferral Partners Back
Contact Us
Global Sales Back
Back
